

EDA NUR DEMIRAY

Tel: 0537 992 21 98

E-mail: edademiray2@gmail.com

Adres: Güngören/İSTANBUL

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a graduate of computer programming. I have experienced many technologies such as unity, C ++, Java, sql, MVC in my education life. My final project was to develop a mobile application with Cordova. I took part in the design of the application with jquery, and in the data extraction with api. In my 4-month internship training, I learned the MVC structure and took an active role in web page development processes. I am currently interested in data science and flutter. And I want to improve myself in this field.

EXPERIENCE

CONTENT TEAM LEADER

İstanbul Bilişim Topluluğu (Mar 2020 - present

- Experience to comminication as a team member
- To organize activities such as a workshop, seminar
- Running all social media operations.

BOARD MEMBER

İstanbul Kültür Üniversitesi DSC (Nov 2019 - present)

- Experience to comminication as a team member
- To organize activities such as a workshop, seminar

INTERNSHIP

Heprix Technology A.Ş (Jan 2019 - May 2019)

- Experience to comminication as a team member
- Learning bootstrap with MVC
- · Active role in web page development processes.

SKİLLS

- C++,Java,Matlab,Sql (Beginner)
- Python (Mid level)
- Flutter (Mid level)
- HTML/CSS/BOOTSTRAP (Mid-High level)

EDUCATION

MATEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

İstanbul Kültür Üniversitesi (2019-present)

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING

İstanbul Kültür Üniversitesi(2016 - 2018)